Contact

romancomer2319@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/roman-comer-782759115 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
TNCC
EMT
Critical Care

Roman Comer

BSN, RN, CCRN-CMC, SRNA

Jackson, Tennessee

Summary

Experienced Intensive Care and Emergency Nurse with a demonstrated history of working within high acuity Intensive Care units and Emergency Departments. Skilled in BLS Instruction, Emergency Medicine, Critical Care, TNCC, Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS), and Neonatal Resuscitation Program (NRP). Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelors Degree in Nursing from the University of Memphis. Actively pursuing my Doctor of Nursing Practice degree in Nurse Anesthesia with an anticipated graduation year of 2022.

Experience

West Tennessee Healthcare Emergency Room Registered Nurse February 2013 - Present (7 years 6 months)

Jackson Madison County General Hospital Cardiovascular ICU Registered Nurse May 2018 - June 2019 (1 year 2 months) Cardiovascular Intensive Care Unit

Regional One Health Trauma Intensive Care Nurse May 2016 - June 2019 (3 years 2 months)

Elvis Presley Memorial Level 1 Trauma Center

Baptist Memorial Health Care Registered Nurse June 2017 - August 2018 (1 year 3 months) Memphis, Tennessee

General Intensive Care Unit

Education

Union University

Doctor of Nursing Practice (DNP), Nurse Anesthesia (CRNA) · (2019 - 2022)

The University of Memphis

Bachelor of Science - BS, Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2017 - 2018)

Jackson State Community College

Associate of Science - AS, Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2013 - 2016)